MATÍAS ZUÑIGA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

■ matiaszuniga93@gmail.com♣ +54 261-6819900♥ Godoy Cruz, Mendoza, Argentina



https://matiasfzuniga.vercel.app

ABOUT ME

I am a fast learner and I am constant.

I have extensive experience handling Adobe packages (photoshop, illustrator, etc).

I have basic knowledge in Linux, tcp/ip protocol and VPS configuration.
Experience in REST architecture and external API's consumption.
Understanding and application of AJAX and web protocols such as HTTP and SSL.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Editor and filmmaker

2012 - 2019

Experience in working collaboratively with teams, dealing directly with end customers and good performance in problem solving.

Developer and web design

Municipalidad de Luján de Cuyo | 2021 -Diciembre 2023 Performing tasks of:

- Maintenance and creation of landings page of the official website of Luján de Cuyo (wordpress and divi).
- Design of informative mailing and newsletter.
- Backend and frontend development with PHP, node, AJAX, jquery, react.
- Basic server configuration (apache, linux).
- SQL database support (mysql, postgre).

TRAINING

Plataforma 5 8

Coding Bootcamp | mayo 2021 - agosto 2021

A total of 800 hours of Javascript oriented content. Using the agile SCRUM methodology, we carry out team projects, fostering leadership and collaboration.

Proyecto ad honorem:

Educational platform for volunteers of an ONG (TECHO), consists of a system of information blocks, managed by user manager (in charge of creating users and administering part of the content) and user admin (in charge of creating users, granting and revoking manager permissions, creating blocks and administering them.

SKILLS

Javascript React Next.js CSS

Node PostgreSQL Express